

Fahmi Nurcahya Software Engineer

🔘 Karawang, Indonesia.

☑ fahminurcahya@gmail.com

© +6285718456591

## PROFILE

3+ years of experience as a Software Engineer, I am skilled in designing, developing, and managing efficient and reliable software solutions.

I possess a profound understanding of modern programming languages, software architecture, and best practices in application development.

I have actively contributed to high-

I have actively contributed to highquality, complex software development projects that meet client needs.

I can understand things quickly and am committed to continuing to learn and develop in the field of technology.

## SOCIAL

- (7) fahminurcahya
- ₩ fahminurcahya
- @ @fahminurcahya

# EDUCATION

Bechelor of Informatic Engineering

> University Of Singaperbangsa Karawang

2015-2019

#### EXPERIENCE

#### MIDDLEWARE DEVELOPER

July 2021 - July 2023

### PT Xsis Mitra Utama, placement at PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia

- Created RestAPI service in ESB to integrate the requirements between BRI channels and third-party entities.
- Integrated applications with various formats such as JSON, ISO, and WSDL.
- Developed stored procedures in SQL Server.
- Acted as a dedicated middleware programmer for the BRI insurance platform (BRISURF).
- Designed the system's application flow, created API specification documentation, and conducted testing.
- Developed dashboard applications using React.js and Express.js.
- Conducted problem-solving and monitored services using Kibana.
- Implemented technologies such as Redis, Kafka, Elasticsearch, Bitbucket, and Bamboo.

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

July 2020 - Juni 2021

### PT Xsis Mitra Utama, placement at PT AZEC Indonesia Management Service

- Developed several dashboard applications using Golang, AngularJS, and Docker as containers for the applications.
- Enhanced new features on existing dashboards using Java.
- Created API services using Golang as the programming language on the server side, with PostgreSQL as the database.

#### BOOTCAMP JAVA DEVELOPER

December 2019 - Juni 2020

### PT Xsis Mitra Utama

- Bootcamp as a java developer

## SKILLS

## Web Apps

HTML5 / CSS / Boostrap
Javascript / Typescript / ReactJs / AngularJS
Node Js / Express Js (ES5/ES6)
PHP (Laravel) / Golang / Java (Spring Boot)
RDBMS(MySQL, SQL Server, PostgreSQL) / MongoDB / Redis

# **Mobile Apps**

Dart / Flutter framework Kotlin / Java

#### **Others**

Git, Docker, Microservices, Product Software AG, Figma / Canva / Adobe llustrator, Firebase, Push Notofication, Adsanse Mobile

PORTOFOLIO

**Show Portofolio**